thefloorpro.com 2014-12-02

# The Floor Pro Privacy Policy - The Floor Pro

## Privacy Policy of The Floor Pro Community

This site collects certain information about you for the purposes of statistics and the administration of the site. This is general information about your browser, your connection and geographical area, but contains no personally identifiable details that you have not voluntarily given. We do keep that information indefinitely, but we do not share it with other organizations, companies or individuals.

If you choose to register for our message boards or directory, we also ask for some additional information, including an email address, which we use to verify your registration request, and to associate you with a particular website account. You can choose to conceal this address from public view. This site will use that address to contact you only for administrative purposes, such as resetting your account password, or notifying you of replies and Personal Messages if you have so indicated in your preferences. We will not sell that address nor share it with other sites EVER.

The software used by this site sets cookies on your computer if you choose to be automatically logged in on each visit. No personally identifiable information beyond your forum identity is contained in this cookie, and we do not share it with other organizations. Certain other sites may attempt to set cookies on your machine as a result of the instant messaging features of the forum software and some sponsor advertising.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, **[read the Google Ads policy here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)**.

Our website contains some affiliate marketing links, which means we get paid commission on sales of those products or services we write about. Our editorial content is not influenced by advertisers or affiliate partnerships. We use a 3rd Party to enable these affiliate partnerships. You can read their **[Privacy Policy](http://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy#users)** and find more information on **[the cookies they use](http://skimlinks.com/user-cookies)**.

Please **[contact the website administrator](http://www.thefloorpro.com/community/sendmessage.php)** if you have any questions or problems concerning The Floor Pro Community or its privacy policy. You can disable features of your forum account at any time by **[modifying your options in the user control panel](http://www.thefloorpro.com/community/profile.php?do=editoptions)** , logging off and not using the account again. Posts made under your account will remain in view at this website even after your account has been disabled.
